CHERQAOUI EL MEHDI

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



CONTACT



+212 678 719 809



chergaoui.elmehdi@gmail.com



www.cherqaoui.dev



79 RUE OUSSAMA BNOU ZAID ETG 2 APPT 3 MAARIF, CASABLANCA

Age: 30 Status: Single

Nationality: Moroccan

Languages: English, French

TECHNOLOGIES

BACKEND











FRONTEND









TOOLS











About Me

A curious, self-motivated Software Developer, driven by the skill of acquiring new skills, I seek to learn and apply my experience in applications design, development and maintenance in order to transform an idea into a working ready to use product. A good communicator and team player.

Work Experience

ECA Assurances 2021-2022

Full Stack Developer

- Building & Maintaining an API for generating quotes and sending customers informations to insurance companies and brokers
- Creating a Dashboard to view the API statistiques (Quotes, ...)

TECHNO: Spring Boot, Angular.

Full Stack Developer

- Building the AUTO Product of Mongustave (website for comparing insurance quotes).
- Integrate & Maintain third party web services in Mongustave (Quotes Providers, insurance companies and brokers).

TECHNO: Laravel, Vuejs.

Alphaboost 2021

Full Stack Developer

- Creating an Ecommerce Store to sell Physical & Subscription products. TECHNO: Laravel, Vuejs, TailwindCSS.

Full Stack Developer

- Creating an application to manage Bookings at various places such as Hotels, Restaurants...

TECHNO: Laravel, jQuery, Bootstrap.

Freelance

2018-2021

Full Stack Developer

- Building a web version of the famous app Popcorn Time. (Featured in my portfolio)

TECHNO: Spring Boot, Angular, RxJS, Typescript, HTML, SASS.

Full Stack Developer

- Building « Streamify » an application to manage and watch Movies & TV shows online. (Featured in my portfolio)

TECHNO: Laravel, Alpinejs, TailwindCSS. **TECHNO:** React, Styled Components.

Frontend Developer

- Creating my portfolio Gatsby js (www.cherqaoui.dev)

TECHNO: Gatsby js, React js, GraphQL, Styled Components, Javascript, JSX.

Android / Spring Developer

- Creating and maintaining a media player app for Android.
- Building a REST API to manage media for the android app.

TECHNO: JAVA Android Studio, Spring Boot

HR Experts

2015-2016

Internship of 5 months as a JAVA Developer

- Creating a JAVA EE web application in order to manage salaries **TECHNO**: JAVA EE, Hibernate, EntityManager, JSP, CSS.

ONDA

2015-2016

Internship of 6 months

- Building a solution to dematerialize the process of invoicing.

TECHNO: JAVA EE, Hibernate, JSP, CSS.

EDUCATION

FST SETTAT

2021-2022

Master Degree in Software Engineering

SUPINFO

2012-2015

Bachelor of Science B.Sc (Bac +4).

Classes Préparatoires

2010-2012

Filière MPSI

Baccalauréat

2009-2010

Sciences Mathématiques Mention bien

HOBBIES

Travel

Fishing

Gaming